(Howard:)and... take a nap.
(Howard:)Really?
(Bernadette:)And miss the keynote?
(Howard:)We can watch it later on C-SPAN.
(Howard:)Besides, I was really
looking forward to you and me...
(Howard:)napping together in the hotel.
(Bernadette:)Honey, if you're
that tired,
(Bernadette:)why don't you just take
a nap here in the car?
(Howard:)No, see, it's not...
(Bernadette:)Hang on.
It's Leonard.
(Bernadette:)Hi, Leonard.
(Penny:)LEONARD
Yeah, hi. Listen, I just
got a text from Raj.
(Leonard(voice):)He wanted me to tell you
that when Howard says "nap,"
he means "sex."
(Bernadette:)Thank you, Raj.
(Leonard:)Are you... an element
in the actinoid series?
(Sheldon:)No.
(Sheldon:)Amy?
(Amy:)Are you usually radioactive
when found in nature?
(Sheldon:)No.
(Amy:)Are you in the
lanthanoid series?
(Sheldon:)Amy, it's Penny's turn.
(Sheldon:)Penny?
(Penny:)Uh, I don't know...
(Penny:)Are you food?
(Sheldon:)That's not apropos.